Hey everyone today it's about something new concerning latex but not from a
design point of view but a technique point of view. As you know I am a latex
crafter myself so I'm always interested in innovations when it comes to latex
sheets, crafting, printing on latex and I received something from Ledapol, a whole
box of prototypes. They have a new innovative way to print on latex and they
wanted to know my opinions so I will show it to you. By the way the dress I'm wearing is also by
Leda Poole and here they 3D printed latex on the mesh and I just love the design and the dress
itself but let's head over to the other pieces. Disclaimer before we are getting into the actual
topic this is probably going to be the only time you will see me wearing natural transparent latex
because I just don't like it to be honest.
It's not my cup of tea at all.
So yeah, I'm not the most enthusiastic person
about this color of latex.
I think LedaPo was inspired by good old 90s
because we have a lot of tribals
and dragons and feathers going on,
but it's about the printing technique
that is really innovative here.
I think I have to show it to you on a separate piece.
So here we have some nice roses.
And maybe you're used to applications that are glued on top of the latex as a second layer.
But the innovation here is that the print is basically integrated or infused into the latex sheet.
so it's one smooth surface and I can also stretch it it does not peel away
and it does not detach itself from each other it's like one layer so this gave me several pieces and
all of them have a bit of a different design I'm going to put on one of the stockings now to show
that they can also print like a big area but just small prints like here
So we have some roses and tribal. I think it's really interesting to see bigger
prints and motifs here and I really like it that there is this possibility now
because normally it is an awful lot of work to put applications on latex or if
you print something on with liquid latex it rubs off so this is really cool maybe
we could use it in a practical way and print on some trims or like I don't know
nice designs. What do you think of this kind of printing technique on latex?
Where do you see this? Do you have any ideas where it could be useful? Let me
know in the comments and let's talk there. I hope you enjoyed this video. It's
really cool to see things that happen in the latex scene and to know what can be
done. Anyway, I will see you in some other videos of mine and I hope you're having a nice day. Bye!